myplick.com 2014-05-16

# myPlick - Privacy Policy

We strongly respect your privacy. Any information we collect, such as operating systems, screen resolution and browser types are used to help make your visit more enjoyable. This Privacy Notice details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the MyPlick Sites. MyPlick provides this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the MyPlick Sites. MyPlick reserves the right to amend the privacy policy any time. 

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the MyPlick Terms of Use. Your use of the MyPlick Sites and any personal information you provide on the MyPlick Sites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use. 

### The Information MyPlick Collects

#### Log File Information

When you use the MyPlick Sites, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

#### Cookies Information

When you visit the MyPlick Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. MyPlick uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the MyPlick Sites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

#### External Links

Myplick contains links to other sites and file downloads from other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such web sites. 

### The Way MyPlick Uses Information

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the MyPlick Sites, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the MyPlick Sites. 

Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload videos or send messages through the MyPlick Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any videos that you submit to the MyPlick Sites may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major MyPlick Site changes or for customer service purposes). 

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the MyPlick Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 

### Our Commitment To Data Security

MyPlick uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to MyPlick and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, MyPlick makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If MyPlick learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. MyPlick may post a notice on the MyPlick Sites if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us using this contact form.
